As an independent channel
because it doesn't make sense.
It's well aligned with
what we are doing with SEO.
And most have expanded their SEO
affordability to integrate AI search
optimization and have also added
strategies existing or planned.
AI search optimization work focuses on
strong data, digital PR and founder
restructuring as we have seen before.
And the goals of AI search optimization
are related to visibility, traffic
run, awardness and conversions.
The biggest challenges
are the ones that surprise surprise, have
to do with measurements
east attribution, data transparency and
tooling because we don't have
direct resources opportunity.
And speaking of tools, these are types of
tools that are being used nowadays for AI
search driving and optimization, AQF
analytics, same results again, not
necessarily different tools than the
one that they apply leveraging for SEO.
So AI search optimization is still massive
and the industry is adapted after
25 years of stable search evolution.
More or less.
Right?
Well, here's a new platform that many,
many more are using for somewhat related
type of needs and we
need to start leveraging.
So it's about aligning and prioritizing
our efforts with your already existing SEO
backlog, SEO initiatives, SEO efforts
to deliver impact that we need today.
And if you want to learn more, because I
know that there are tons of resources
here, you have this free checklist that
you can download directly with all of
these resources I have created a website
completely free, completely free resources
and reliable resources that
is called learningaisearch.
com as well.
And you can keep up with everything that
happens with AI search with the SEO
coholes in our guide
and there's an AI search section there.
Last but not least at last,
GEO is that low Life SEO for AI.
TikTok, YouTube, whatever
platform the user used to search.
Google T Optimize.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
She wins the contest for most keywords
and all of the slides there, right?
Maybe just most words, who knows?
All right, we are moving into the first
panel of our conference today here.
So as our staff, the first.